Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations: an inventory
Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations
- Equatorial, Volume 3, 1855-01-13/1856-04-01; phaedra0173 (Box 4)
  KG11365.173
  H19
  Contributor: J.F. Flagg
  J.F. Flagg
  George Phillips Bond, Philip Sidney Coolidge, William Cranch Bond, Charles W. Tuttle, Truman Henry Safford
  Observations: Saturn; Occultation of 19 Cancri by the Moon; Occultation of Uranus; Procyon; Occultation of Venus; Occultation of 46 Leonis; Personal Equation between W.C.B. and P.S.C.; Jupiter; Conjunction of Satellites; Neptune; Venus; Mars; Stars in the vicinity of Procyon; Ephemeris of de Vico Comet for 1855.
  Newspaper cutting pasted onto inner back cover: Nantucket Inquirer; Friday, Dec. 14, 1855: Letter to the Editor on discovery of a comet
  Images: Jupiter; Saturn; Saturn (Humorous); Star maps; insect; Manicules; Moon rising Nov 27...drawn from nature
- Equatorial, 1856-04-01/1857-02-15; phaedra0174 (Box 4)
  KG11365.174
  H20
- Equatorial, 1857-02-15/1857-05-13; phaedra0175 (Box 4)
  KG11365.175
  H21
- Equatorial, 1857-05-13/1857-08-23; phaedra0176 (Box 4)
  KG11365.176
  H22
- Equatorial, 1857-08-23/1857-10-20; phaedra0177 (Box 4)
  KG11365.177
  H23
- Equatorial, 1857-10-20/1857-12-15; phaedra0178 (Box 4)
  KG11365.178
  H24
- Equatorial, 1857-12-15/1858-03-18; phaedra0179 (Box 4)
  KG11365.179
  H25
  1857phae.proj..179.
- Equatorial, 1858-03-18/1858-07-14; phaedra0180 (Box 4)
  KG11365.180
  H26
- Equatorial, 1858-07-14/1858-09-25; phaedra0181 (Box 4)
  KG11365.181
  H27
- Equatorial, 1858-09-25/1858-11-11; phaedra0182 (Box 4)
  KG11365.182
  H28
  Contributor: Selina C. Bond
  Selina C. Bond
  George Phillips Bond, Richard F. Bond, William Cranch Bond, Horace P. Tuttle, Truman Henry Safford
  Observations: Donati's Comet; Asteroid Searle; Photography; Tuttle Comet VII; Searle's Planet; Collection of Memoranda relating to naked eye view of Comet of Donati in Sept. & Oct. 1858; [newsprint clipping] Boston Daily Advertiser: The Great Comet of 1858; ephemeris of Mr. Schubert's Asteroid; Ephemeris of Comet VIII; Ephemeris of Comet V
  Numerous sketches of Comet of Donati
- Equatorial, 1858-11-11/1859-05-04; phaedra0183 (Box 5)
  KG11365.183
  H29
- Equatorial, 1859-05-04/1859-10-26; phaedra0184 (Box 5)
  KG11365.184
  H30
- Equatorial, 1859-10-26/1860-01-31; phaedra0185 (Box 5)
  KG11365.185
  H31
- Equatorial, 1860-01-31/1860-03-15; phaedra0186 (Box 5)
  KG11365.186
  H32
- Equatorial, 1860-03-15/1860-03-30; phaedra0187 (Box 5)
  KG11365.187
  H33
- Equatorial, 1860-03-30/1860-05-02; phaedra0188 (Box 5)
  KG11365.188
  H34
- Equatorial, 1860-05-02/1860-06-24; phaedra0189 (Box 5)
  KG11365.189
  H35
- Equatorial, 1860-06-24/1860-07-04; phaedra0190 (Box 5)
  KG11365.190
  H36
- Equatorial, 1860-07-04/1860-09-26; phaedra0191 (Box 5)
  KG11365.191
  H37
- Equatorial, 1860-09-26/1861-01-31; phaedra0192 (Box 5)
  KG11365.192
  H38
- Equatorial, 1861-01-31/1861-04-09; phaedra0193 (Box 5)
  KG11365.193
  H39
- Equatorial, 1861-04-09/1861-05-03; phaedra0194 (Box 5)
  KG11365.194
  H40
- Equatorial, 1861-05-03/1861-06-22; phaedra0195 (Box 5)
  KG11365.195
  H41
- Equatorial, 1861-06-22/1861-07-13; phaedra0196 (Box 5)
  KG11365.196
  H42
- Equatorial, 1861-07-13/1861-09-16; phaedra0197 (Box 5)
  KG11365.197
  H43
- Equatorial, 1861-09-16/1862-01-01; phaedra0198 (Box 5)
  KG11365.198
  H44
- Equatorial, 1862-01-01/1862-04-19; phaedra0199 (Box 5)
  KG11365.199
  H45
- Equatorial, 1862-04-19/1862-07-06; phaedra0200 (Box 5)
  KG11365.200
  H46
- Equatorial, 1862-07-06/1862-08-19; phaedra0201 (Box 5)
  KG11365.201
  H47
- Equatorial, 1862-08-19/1862-12-06; phaedra0202 (Box 5)
  KG11365.202
  H48
- Equatorial, 1862-12-06/1863-04-13; phaedra0203 (Box 5)
  KG11365.203
  H49
- Equatorial, 1863-04-13/1863-06-10; phaedra0204 (Box 5)
  KG11365.204
  H50
- Equatorial, 1863-06-10/1863-10-05; phaedra0205 (Box 5)
  KG11365.205
  H51
- Equatorial, 1863-10-05/1864-02-19; phaedra0206 (Box 5)
  KG11365.206
  H52
- Equatorial, 1864-02-19/1864-03-21; phaedra0207 (Box 5)
  KG11365.207
  H53
- Equatorial, 1864-03-21/1864-06-01; phaedra0208 (Box 5)
  KG11365.208
  H54
- Equatorial, 1864-06-01/1865-04-03; phaedra0209 (Box 5)
  KG11365.209
  H55
- Equatorial, 1865-04-03/1866-02-05; phaedra0210 (Box 5)
  KG11365.210
  H56
  Equatorial series begins again at KG11365.284 (N1)
- Zones 1-7, 1852-04-07/1852-05-04; phaedra0211 (Box 5)
  KG11365.211
  K1
- Zones 7-13, 1852-05-04/1852-11-04; phaedra0212 (Box 5)
  KG11365.212
  K2
- Zones 14-19, Bessel, 1852-11-04/1852-12-15; phaedra0213 (Box 5)
  KG11365.213
  K3
- Zones 20-26, 1852-12-15/1853-01-11; phaedra0214 (Box 5)
  KG11365.214
  K4
- Zones 27-33, 1853-01-11/1853-02-12; phaedra0215 (Box 5)
  KG11365.215
  K5
- Zones 34-39, 1853-02-12/1853-03-16; phaedra0216 (Box 5)
  KG11365.216
  K6
- Zones 40-45, 1853-03-16/1853-04-08; phaedra0217 (Box 5)
  KG11365.217
  K7
- Zones 46-54, 1853-04-08/1854-12-08; phaedra0218 (Box 5)
  KG11365.218
  K8
- Zones 55-62, 1853-05-31/1854-09-27; phaedra0219 (Box 5)
  KG11365.219
  K9
- Zones 65-84a, 1854-09-27/1854-12-08; phaedra0220 (Box 5)
  KG11365.220
  K10
- Zones 84a-88, 1854-12-08/1855-02-12; phaedra0221 (Box 5)
  KG11365.221
  K11
- Zones 89-100, 1855-02-12/1855-04-23; phaedra0222 (Box 5)
  KG11365.222
  K12
- Zones 101-116, 1855-04-23/1855-07-17; phaedra0223 (Box 5)
  KG11365.223
  K13
- Zones 1-6, 1859-03-30/1859-05-03; phaedra0224 (Box 5)
  KG11365.224
  K14
- Zones 6-7, 1859-05-03/1859-05-23; phaedra0225 (Box 5)
  KG11365.225
  K15
- Zones 117-124, 1859-05-23/1859-08-29; phaedra0226 (Box 6)
  KG11365.226
  K16
- Zones 125-135, 1859-08-29/1859-11-26; phaedra0227 (Box 6)
  KG11365.227
  K17
- Zones 134-146, 1859-11-26/1860-02-21; phaedra0228 (Box 6)
  KG11365.228
  K18
- Zones 147-149, 1860-02-21/1860-11-20; phaedra0229 (Box 6)
  KG11365.229
  K19
- Zones, 1860-02-26/1860-11-20; phaedra0230 (Box 6)
  KG11365.230
  K20
- Zones, 1860-02-26/1861-04-08; phaedra0231 (Box 6)
  KG11365.231
  K21
- Zones, 1861-04-08/1861-07-11; phaedra0232 (Box 6)
  KG11365.232
  K22
- Zones, 1861-07-11/1861-09-24; phaedra0233 (Box 6)
  KG11365.233
  K23
- Zones, 1861-09-24/1862-10-22; phaedra0234 (Box 6)
  KG11365.234
  K24
- Zones, 1862-10-22/1863-02-18; phaedra0235 (Box 6)
  KG11365.235
  K25
- Zones, 1863-02-18/1864-06-23; phaedra0236 (Box 6)
  KG11365.236
  K26
- Zones, 1864-06-23/1864-09-27; phaedra0237 (Box 6)
  KG11365.237
  K27
- Reduction of Zone Observations, 1853; phaedra0238 (Box 6)
  KG11365.238
  L1
- Zones, 1864-10-05/1864-12-01; phaedra0239 (Box 6)
  KG11365.239
  K28
- Reduction of Zone Observations, 1853; phaedra0240 (Box 6)
  KG11365.240
  L2
- Reduction of Zone Observations, 1853; phaedra0241 (Box 6)
  KG11365.241
  L3
- Reduction of Zone Observations, 1853; phaedra0242 (Box 6)
  KG11365.242
  L4
- Reduction of Zone Observations, 1853; phaedra0243 (Box 6)
  KG11365.243
  L5
- Reduction of Zone Observations, 1853; phaedra0244 (Box 6)
  KG11365.244
  L6
- Reduction of Zone Observations, phaedra0245 (Box 6)
  KG11365.245
  L7
- Reduction of Zone Observations, phaedra0246 (Box 6)
  KG11365.246
  L8
- Comparisons of Zones, phaedra0247 (Box 6)
  KG11365.247
  L9
- Reductions of Zones No Reductions, 1859; phaedra0248 (Box 6)
  KG11365.248
  L10
- Reductions of Zones Comparison of Magnitudes, 1859; phaedra0249 (Box 6)
  KG11365.249
  L11
- Special Zones and Magnitudes, phaedra0250 (Box 6)
  KG11365.250
  L12
- Revision of Zones Magnitudes, phaedra0251 (Box 6)
  KG11365.251
  L13
- Reduction of Zones I, phaedra0252 (Box 6)
  KG11365.252
  M2
- Gould's Universal Index, phaedra0253 (Box 6)
  KG11365.253
  M3
- [Tables, Procedures], phaedra0254 (Box 6)
  KG11365.254
  M5
- Table of Contents of various books containing records of observations, 1841/1855; phaedra0255 (Box 6)
  KG11365.255
  M6
- Various memoranda [Longitude determination, mag. Measure, etc.], 1844/1855; phaedra0256 (Box 6)
  KG11365.256
  M7
- Catalog Stars, 1854/1858; phaedra0257 (Box 6)
  KG11365.257
  M9
- Tables for apportioning Instrumental Corrections, 1855; phaedra0258 (Box 6)
  KG11365.258
  M10
- Catalogue of Stars for Zones, 1853; phaedra0259 (Box 6)
  KG11365.259
  M11
- Reduction of Stars from 0 to 1 degrees, 1853; phaedra0260 (Box 7)
  KG11365.260
  M12
  1853phae.proj..260.
- Printing of Publications (Zone Observations; and History and Description of the Observatory), 1854/1857; phaedra0261 (Box 7)
  KG11365.261
  M13
  1854phae.proj..261.
- Lists of persons and Institution recipients of HCO Annals, 1859/1875-09-24; phaedra0262 (Box 7)
  KG11365.262
  M14
  1859phae.proj..262.
- Meteorological Records, 1861-01-01/1863-05-01; phaedra0263 (Box 7)
  KG11365.263
  M15
  1861phae.proj..263.
- 1859-60 Comet Seeker, 1859-12-01/1860-09-11; phaedra0264 (Box 7)
  KG11365.264
  M16
  Horace P. Tuttle, George Phillips Bond
  1859phae.proj..264T
  Contains comet sketches, and newspaper clippings
- Colorado Survey - Time, 1857-12-13/1858-05-23; phaedra0265 (Box 7)
  KG11365.265
  M17
  Field director: Joseph Christmas Ives
  Field director:
  Joseph Christmas Ives
  George Phillips Bond
  1857phae.proj..265B
- Colorado Survey - Latitude by Polaris, 1857-12-13/1858-05-23; phaedra0266 (Box 7)
  KG11365.266
  M18
  1857phae.proj..266B
- [Solar Observations], 1855-01-05/1855-05-02; phaedra0267 (Box 7)
  KG11365.267
  M19
  1855phae.proj..267.
  Contains sketches of sunspots; some notes in french.
- [Comet Seeking], 1850-06-16/1853-05-01; phaedra0268 (Box 7)
  KG11365.268
  M20
  1850phae.proj..268T
- [Comet Seeking], 1847-06-10/1850-06-05; phaedra0269 (Box 7)
  KG11365.269
  M21
  1847phae.proj..269B
- Books received at the Observatory of Harvard College, 1862-01-06/1878-11-12; phaedra0270 (Box 7)
  KG11365.270
  M23
  Harvard College Observatory. Phillips Library
  1862phae.proj..270.
- Reductions of Moon Culminations, 1849-01-01/1852-05-28; phaedra0271 (Box 7)
  KG11365.271
  M24
  1849phae.proj..271S
- Reductions of Moon Culminations, 1851-07-01/1854-10-02; phaedra0272 (Box 7)
  KG11365.272
  M25
  1851phae.proj..272B
- P.S.N [drawings of star configuration and angles], 1856-06-16/1856-07-04; phaedra0273 (Box 7)
  KG11365.273
  M26
  Philip Sidney Coolidge
  1856phae.proj..273C
- P.S.N [drawings of star configuration and angles], 1850-11-15/1851-08-22; phaedra0274 (Box 7)
  KG11365.274
  M27
  1850phae.proj..274T
  Contains notes on 7/28/1851 Solar Eclipse, and 8/22/1851 Tornado
- Subscribers to "The Account of Comet 1858"" and others", 1858/1877; phaedra0275 (Box 7)
  KG11365.275
  M28
  1858phae.proj..275.
  Contains frontmatter of Gould's Universal Index (1848)
- Printing, 1860-04-14/1863-08-24; phaedra0276 (Box 7)
  KG11365.276
  M29
  1860phae.proj..276B
  Contains plate reproductions of comet illustrations (Donati - 1858)
- Memoranda for Observatory Report, 1861-01-07/1864-12-31; phaedra0277 (Box 7)
  KG11365.277
  M30
  1861phae.proj..277B
  Contains newpaper clippings
- Memoranda, 1862-01-03/1865-01-02; phaedra0278 (Box 7)
  KG11365.278
  M31
  1862phae.proj..278B
- Catalog of Books in the Phillips Library, 1856-10-09/1877-06-04; phaedra0279 (Box 7)
  KG11365.279
  M32
  1856phae.proj..279.
- Chronometer - Stars, 1862/1865; phaedra0280 (Box 7)
  KG11365.280
  M33
  Joseph Winlock
  1862phae.proj..280W
- Transit Catalog, 1863-01-12; phaedra0281 (Box 7)
  KG11365.281
  M34
  1863phae.proj..281.
- Eclipse of 4/25/1864 - Portland, 1846-04-25; phaedra0282 (Box 7)
  KG11365.282
  M35
  Charles Henry Davis
  1846phae.proj..282D
- Account of Various Records and Papers belonging to the Observatory, 1866/1877; phaedra0283 (Box 7)
  KG11365.283
  M36
  1866phae.proj..283S
  Contains information about the original alphabetical sequence cataloging for these books prior to 1877
- Observations with East Equatorial, 1866-06-09/1866-07-09; phaedra0284 (Box 7)
  KG11365.284
  N1
  Joseph Winlock, Samuel Pierpont Langley, George M. Searle
  1866phae.proj..284W
  Contains sketches of Saturn and moons
- Observations with East Equatorial, 1866-07-09/1866-07-24; phaedra0285 (Box 7)
  KG11365.285
  N2
  Samuel Pierpont Langley, Joseph Winlock, George M. Searle
  1866phae.proj..285L
- Observations with East Equatorial, 1866-07-24/1866-08-13; phaedra0286 (Box 7)
  KG11365.286
  N3
  1866phae.proj..286L
- Observations with East Equatorial, 1866-08-13/1866-08-26; phaedra0287 (Box 7)
  KG11365.287
  N4
  1866phae.proj..287L
  Contains sketch of Trifid Nebula
- Observations with East Equatorial, 1866-08-26/1866-09-12; phaedra0288 (Box 7)
  KG11365.288
  N5
  George M. Searle, Joseph Winlock, Samuel Pierpont Langley
  1866phae.proj..288S
- Observations with East Equatorial, 1866-09-12/1866-10-02; phaedra0289 (Box 7)
  KG11365.289
  N6
  Joseph Winlock, George M. Searle
  1866phae.proj..289W
- Observations with East Equatorial, 1866-10-02/1866-10-22; phaedra0290 (Box 7)
  KG11365.290
  N7
  George M. Searle, Joseph Winlock
  1866phae.proj..290S
- Observations with East Equatorial, 1866-10-22/1867-01-23; phaedra0291 (Box 7)
  KG11365.291
  N8
  1866phae.proj..291W
- Observations with East Equatorial, 1867-01-23/1867-04-25; phaedra0292 (Box 7)
  KG11365.292
  N9
  1867phae.proj..292S
  Contains small sketches of planets, moon craters
- Observations with East Equatorial, 1867-04-25/1867-10-25; phaedra0293 (Box 7)
  KG11365.293
  N10
  1867phae.proj..293S
- Observations with East Equatorial, 1867-10-25/1868-01-27; phaedra0294 (Box 7)
  KG11365.294
  N11
  George M. Searle, Charles S. Peirce
  1867phae.proj..294S
- Observations with East Equatorial, 1868-01-27/1868-04-01; phaedra0295 (Box 7)
  KG11365.295
  N12
  1868phae.proj..295S
- Equatorial [Spectra], 1868-04-01/1868-10-10; phaedra0296 (Box 8)
  KG11365.296
  N13
- Equatorial, 1868-10-10/1868-12-22; phaedra0297 (Box 8)
  KG11365.297
  N14
- Equatorial, 1868-12-22/1869-04-28; phaedra0298 (Box 8)
  KG11365.298
  N15
- Equatorial, 1869-04-28/1869-10-14; phaedra0299 (Box 8)
  KG11365.299
  N16
- Equatorial, 1869-10-14/1871-10-31; phaedra0300 (Box 8)
  KG11365.300
  N17
- Equatorial Miscellaneous Observations, 1869-12-24/1871-10-31; phaedra0301 (Box 8)
  KG11365.301
  N18
- Equatorial Miscellaneous Observations, 1869-12-24/1874-12-08; phaedra0302 (Box 8)
  KG11365.302
  N19
- Equatorial Miscellaneous Observations, 1870-07-13/1874-12-08; phaedra0303 (Box 8)
  KG11365.303
  N20
- Asteroids, 1870-07-13/1871-02-13; phaedra0304 (Box 8)
  KG11365.304
  N21
- Asteroids, 1871-02-13/1871-08-10; phaedra0305 (Box 8)
  KG11365.305
  N22
- Asteroids, phaedra0306 (Box 8)
  KG11365.306
  N23
  William A. Rogers
- Asteroids, phaedra0307 (Box 8)
  KG11365.307
  N24
- Reduction of Asteroid Observations, 1870; phaedra0308 (Box 8)
  KG11365.308
  N25
- Reduction of Asteroid Observations, 1870/1871; phaedra0309 (Box 8)
  KG11365.309
  N26
- Reduction to apparent place of some stars used in 1870, phaedra0310 (Box 8)
  KG11365.310
  N27
- Reduction to apparent place of some stars used in 1870, phaedra0311 (Box 8)
  KG11365.311
  N28
- Reduction of Asteroid Observations, 1870; phaedra0312 (Box 8)
  KG11365.312
  N29
- Search for Asteroids, 1870; phaedra0313 (Box 8)
  KG11365.313
  N30
- Equatorial - observations of asteroids and comets, phaedra0314 (Box 8)
  KG11365.314
  N31
- Computation of apparent place and differentiated refraction, 1866-04-26/1866-06-30; phaedra0315 (Box 8)
  KG11365.315
  N32
- Reduction of Equatorial Observations, 1866-08-26/1866-10-15; phaedra0316 (Box 8)
  KG11365.316
  N33
- Equatorial (copy), 1866-04-09/1866-08-26; phaedra0317 (Box 8)
  KG11365.317
  N34
- Equatorial (copy), 1866-08-27/1866-10-21; phaedra0318 (Box 8)
  KG11365.318
  N35
- Equatorial (copy), 1866-10-21/1867-01-14; phaedra0319 (Box 8)
  KG11365.319
  N36
- Equatorial (copy), 1867-01-14/1867-04-26; phaedra0320 (Box 8)
  KG11365.320
  N37
- Equatorial (copy), 1867-04-26/1867-10-22; phaedra0321 (Box 8)
  KG11365.321
  N38
- Equatorial (copy), 1867-10-22/1868-02-03; phaedra0322 (Box 8)
  KG11365.322
  N39
- Equatorial (copy), 1868-02-03/1868-06-28; phaedra0323 (Box 8)
  KG11365.323
  N40
- Catalog of Nebulae, phaedra0324 (Box 8)
  KG11365.324
  N41
- Measurement of photographs of eclipse, 1869/1870; phaedra0325 (Box 8)
  KG11365.325
  N42
- Measurement of photographs of solar eclipse, 1870; phaedra0326 (Box 8)
  KG11365.326
  N43
- Notes to sketches of sun by E.L. Trouvelot, 1870-10-30/1873-04-14; phaedra0327 (Box 8)
  KG11365.327
  N44
  Etienne Leopold Trouvelot
- Notes to sketches of sun by E.L. Trouvelot, 1873-04-14/1874-09-30; phaedra0328 (Box 8)
  KG11365.328
  N45
- Solar Photography, 1870-07-04/1876-11-30; phaedra0329 (Box 8)
  KG11365.329
  N46
- General Record of Work done with the East Equatorial, 1869/1872; phaedra0330 (Box 8)
  KG11365.329.5
  N48
- Tables, etc., 1866/1867; phaedra0331 (Box 8)
  KG11365.330
  N50
- Reduced Measures of Double Stars - Equatorial, 1866/1867; phaedra0332 (Box 8)
  KG11365.331
  N51
- East Transit Observations, 1866-05-01/1866-09-04; phaedra0333 (Box 8)
  KG11365.332
  O1
- East Transit Observations, 1866-09-04/1867-05-31; phaedra0334 (Box 8)
  KG11365.333
  O2
- East Transit Observations, 1867-05-31/1867-11-09; phaedra0335 (Box 8)
  KG11365.334
  O3
- East Transit Observations, 1867-11-09/1868-07-16; phaedra0336 (Box 9)
  KG11365.335
  O4
- East Transit Observations, 1868-07-16/1868-10-03; phaedra0337 (Box 9)
  KG11365.336
  O5
- East Transit Observations (time), 1868-10-03/1869-08-29; phaedra0338 (Box 9)
  KG11365.337
  O6
- East Transit Observations (time), 1869-08-29/1870-06-12; phaedra0339 (Box 9)
  KG11365.338
  O7
- East Transit Observations (Occultations), 1870-06-12/1871-12-01; phaedra0340 (Box 9)
  KG11365.339
  O8
- East Transit Observations (time), 1871-12-01/1871-12-27; phaedra0341 (Box 9)
  KG11365.340
  O9
- Chronograph Record, 1866-04-02/1869-07-29; phaedra0342 (Box 9)
  KG11365.341
  O10
- East Transit (errors), 1866-04-17/1867-09-17; phaedra0343 (Box 9)
  KG11365.342
  O11
- Longitude Campaign: Cambridge - Washington, 1867; phaedra0344 (Box 9)
  KG11365.343
  O12
- Transit Observations, 1867-06-28/1867-06-29; phaedra0345 (Box 9)
  KG11365.344
  O13
- Formulae for Reduction of Transit Observations and Tables, 1867; phaedra0346 (Box 9)
  KG11365.345
  O14
- Chronograph Record, 1867-07-31/1867-12-19; phaedra0347 (Box 9)
  KG11365.346
  O15
- Chronograph Record, 1867-12-19/1868-08-04; phaedra0348 (Box 9)
  KG11365.347
  O16
- Chronograph Record, 1868-08-04/1869-08-13; phaedra0349 (Box 9)
  KG11365.348
  O17
- Chronograph Record, 1869-08-13/1870-07-07; phaedra0350 (Box 9)
  KG11365.349
  O18
- Record of Errors of Clocks, 1866/1869; phaedra0351 (Box 9)
  KG11365.350
  O19
- Stars to be observed with East Transit, 1868/1870; phaedra0352 (Box 9)
  KG11365.351
  O20?
- Second Computation of Instrument Errors, 1867/1868; phaedra0353 (Box 9)
  KG11365.352
  O20
- Longitudes Computations from Coast Survey, 1869; phaedra0354 (Box 9)
  KG11365.353
  O21
- [Transit Observations], 1870-08-24/1870-10-23; phaedra0355 (Box 9)
  KG11365.354
  O22
- Longitude - Field Reductions, 1871; phaedra0356 (Box 9)
  KG11365.355
  O23
- Clock Corrections, 1869/1872; phaedra0357 (Box 9)
  KG11365.356
  O24
- Clock Corrections, 1872/1875; phaedra0358 (Box 9)
  KG11365.357
  O25
- Clock Corrections, 1875; phaedra0359 (Box 9)
  KG11365.358
  O26
- Notes on Astronomy Engravings, Spanish Weather Record, Phillips Fund, phaedra0360 (Box 9)
  KG11365.359
  O27
- Eclipse of 1869, Reports, phaedra0361 (Box 9)
  KG11365.360
  O28
- Personal equation observations, 1871; phaedra0362 (Box 9)
  KG11365.361
  O29
- Magnetic Observations, 1866-08-16/1868-02-17; phaedra0363 (Box 9)
  KG11365.362
  P1
- Meteorological Observations, 1866; phaedra0364 (Box 9)
  KG11365.363
  P2
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1866; phaedra0365 (Box 9)
  KG11365.364
  P3
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1867; phaedra0366 (Box 9)
  KG11365.365
  P4
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1868; phaedra0367 (Box 9)
  KG11365.366
  P5
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1869; phaedra0368 (Box 9)
  KG11365.367
  P6
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1870; phaedra0369 (Box 9)
  KG11365.368
  P7
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1871; phaedra0370 (Box 10)
  KG11365.369
  P8
  Clayton Octavo
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1872; phaedra0371 (Box 10)
  KG11365.370
  P9
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1873; phaedra0372 (Box 10)
  KG11365.371
  P10
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1874; phaedra0373 (Box 10)
  KG11365.372
  P11
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1875; phaedra0374 (Box 10)
  KG11365.373
  P12
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1876; phaedra0375 (Box 10)
  KG11365.374
  P13
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1877; phaedra0376 (Box 10)
  KG11365.375
  P14
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1878; phaedra0377 (Box 10)
  KG11365.376
  P15
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1879; phaedra0378 (Box 10)
  KG11365.377
  P16
- Meteorological Record of HCO, 1866/1868; phaedra0379 (Box 10)
  KG11365.378
  Q1
- Meteorological Record of HCO, 1869; phaedra0380 (Box 10)
  KG11365.379
  Q2
- Meteorological Record of HCO, 1870/1871; phaedra0381 (Box 10)
  KG11365.380
  Q3
- Meteorological Record of HCO, 1872/1875; phaedra0382 (Box 10)
  KG11365.381
  Q4
- Meteorological Record of HCO, 1866/1879; phaedra0383 (Box 10)
  Date:
  Bulk of observations from 1878-1879
  KG11365.382
  Q5
- Mr. J.G. Homer's Original Minutes of Chronometer Expedition, 1857; phaedra0384 (Box 10)
  KG11365.383
- A___ A____ of the White Mts. Of New Hampshire (n.b. Annular Eclipse), 1853; phaedra0385 (Box 10)
  KG11365.384
- [Paris to Cambridge Telegraph], 1861; phaedra0386 (Box 10)
  KG11365.385
- U.S. Coast Survey, Benjamin Pierce, Subplot: Letter Book and Abstract - Long Party, 1868; phaedra0387 (Box 10)
  KG11365.386
- Observations and Longitude Computations (U.S. Coast Survey), 1872; phaedra0388 (Box 10)
  KG11365.387
- Longitude and Latitude no. 1 (Bolivia), 1892/1893; phaedra0389 (Box 10)
  KG11365.388
- Time Service, 1880-04-18/1881-04-19; phaedra0390 (Box 10)
  KG11365.389
- Meridian Circle Record - Mr. Austin, 1870-08-16/1871-05-13; phaedra0391 (Box 10)
  KG11365.390
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-03-06/1872-03-22; phaedra0392 (Box 10)
  KG11365.391
  Vol. 1
  Charles S. Peirce
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-03-22/1872-06-06; phaedra0393 (Box 10)
  KG11365.392
  Vol. 2
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-06-06/1872-07-02; phaedra0394 (Box 10)
  KG11365.393
  Vol. 3
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-05-04/1872-05-31; phaedra0395 (Box 10)
  KG11365.394
  Vol. 4
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-05-31/1872-06-10; phaedra0396 (Box 10)
  KG11365.395
  Vol. 5
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-06-10/1872-06-30; phaedra0397 (Box 10)
  KG11365.396
  Vol. 6
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-06-30/1872-07-30; phaedra0398 (Box 10)
  KG11365.397
  Vol. 7
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-07-30/1872-08-09; phaedra0399 (Box 10)
  KG11365.398
  Vol. 8
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-08-09/1872-08-18; phaedra0400 (Box 10)
  KG11365.399
  Vol. 9
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-08-18/1873-03-09; phaedra0401 (Box 11)
  KG11365.400
  Vol. 10
  1872phae.proj..401P
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1873-03-09/1873-06-08; phaedra0402 (Box 11)
  KG11365.401
  Vol. 11
  1873phae.proj..402P
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1873-06-08/1873-09-06; phaedra0403 (Box 11)
  KG11365.402
  Vol. 12
  1873phae.proj..403P
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1873-09-06/1873-09-22; phaedra0404 (Box 11)
  KG11365.403
  Vol. 13
  1873phae.proj..404P
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1873-09-22/1873-09-30; phaedra0405 (Box 11)
  KG11365.404
  Vol. 14
  1873phae.proj..405P
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1873-09-30/1873-10-11; phaedra0406 (Box 11)
  KG11365.405
  Vol. 15
  1873phae.proj..406P
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1873-10-11/1874-04-13; phaedra0407 (Box 11)
  KG11365.406
  Vol. 16